{
    "subject": "resource/January_07003:_Bell_Studies_for_the_Clock_of_the_Long_Now",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Brian_Eno",
    "human_readable": "The producer of January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now is Brian Eno.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9086207747459412,
            "question": "Who produced 'Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8740304112434387,
            "question": "What year was 'Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now' produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6826424598693848,
            "question": "What type of work is 'Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6822218894958496,
            "question": "What is the name of the piece composed by Brian Eno for 'The Clock of the Long Now'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6357792019844055,
            "question": "What project is the piece 'Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now' associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5773022174835205,
            "question": "How might 'Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now' be used in relation to its associated project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4605638086795807,
            "question": "What is 'The Clock of the Long Now'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41139107942581177,
            "question": "Has Brian Eno produced other works besides music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2922607660293579,
            "question": "Is Brian Eno known for composing music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28966206312179565,
            "question": "What does Brian Eno do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of January 07003: Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now is Brian Eno.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3151_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Brian Eno known for composing music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3151_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Brian Eno produced other works besides music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3151_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is 'The Clock of the Long Now'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3151_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3151_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents confirm that Brian Eno produced and released an album titled \"January 07003, Bell Studies for the Clock of the Long Now,\" as stated in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}